[Music]
[âm nhạc]
ha
ha
[Applause] The
[Vỗ tay]
first to emerge from heaven, the magnificent realm of the
đầu xuất thiên cùng cảnh giới nguy
beautiful and graceful Southern Goddess, the Southern Goddess, the
nga thên nữ đẹp thướt tha Thiên Nam Sắc
heavenly music resounds with
dạng người nhạc Trời trối xộn vang từng
countless joyful songs, the
bừng muôn khúc Hoan
Bodhisattva protects the world, the waves of the Sin Ci lute,
Ca Bồ Tát hộ Minh sóng đàn Sin ci ta
the time has come, eight people cross over, calling
bà thời đã tới tám nhân xuyên gọi mơi
from ancient India, the faithful people are
nơi xư Ấn Độ cổ xưa dân Trung Tín hưa
happy and hopeful, the city is a place of enlightenment, the lineage of the noble and virtuous
vui tu mong Câ thành phầ nhưng lạc lối
avoids the
mê l dòng họ thích ca cao quy tránh vị
queen, the love of Khoi has a vow, the
hoàng hậu ma g tình Khôi có lời nguyền
Thanh Buddha Mother,
ông Thanh Phật
on the bright day, the
Mẫu ngày thàng Sáng
beautiful dawn, the mountains stop where the emergence comes, the
xin bình minh tươi đẹp núi dừng nơi xuất
sound of the heavenly
xa hòa vang tiếng Thiên
body, the Bodhi tree has attained enlightenment, the great and high, the birds are
thân cội bồ đề thành đạo đã lớn cao chim
happy,
vui
welcoming the heavens.
con đón trờ
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
Three people, the legend, calling, inviting the Heavenly
Tam nhân Xên huyền thoại gọi mời Thiên
Lord, the Bodhisattva protects the world, the
chủ Bồ Tát hộ Minh Đàn Sinh cối ta bà
C Tỳ La returns, the disciples, the many
dừng vô yêu C Tỳ La về thi tử tất đàn đa
disciples, the Buddha Shakyamuni.
đàn sinh cối ta bà Phật Thích Ca
[Music] The
[âm nhạc]
heavenly palace, the Southern Goddess, a hundred righteous paths,
Cung trời đầ xó Thiên Nữ Thiên Nam trăm
joyful, the pure and noble, eight
t Bá Chánh Đạo vui Hì Lạc Thanh Cao tám
people return, the vow, the Bodhisattva protects the world, the
nhân duyên hồi đua thề chủ Bồ Tát hộ
responsibility of the disciples, saving the world of the Saha, the
Minh Tránh nhiệm Đàn Sinh cứu khổ cõi Ta
disciples, the Buddha Shakyamuni.
Bà thi tử tất đàn đa Phật Thích Ca
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
Eight people reincarnated, racing to the Heavenly Lord, Bodhisattva
tám nhân xyên hồi Đua Thiên chủ Bồ Tát
protecting the bright right mindfulness, the altar of birth saving the suffering of the Saha world, the womb advancing, the
hộ minh chánh niệm Đàn Sinh cứu khổ cõi
altar of
Ta Bà thai tử tấn đàn
many Buddhas, worldly song.
đa Phật thế ca
Oh
Oh
[Music] [
[âm nhạc]
K
K